buyessayfriend.com 2019-01-07

# Writing Service BuyEssayFriend: Our Privacy Policy

BuyEssayFriend wants to make sure that our users have a secure and safe access to the services we provide. We encourage you to take your time and be sure that you understand exactly how we gather and use your personal data such that you feel comfortable providing us with such information.

If you don’t agree with any of the points highlighted in this Privacy Policy, then you should not use our service. If you have any questions about the terms, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact the Customer Support via email: support@buyessayfriend.com.

## The Reasons Why We Gather and Process Your Personal Information

We only use your personal information for legal reasons and in accordance to the data protection law. Our purposes are as follows:

  * To contact you in relation to the ordering and writing process;
  * To notify you about any changes that relate to our services;
  * To process refunds, payments and sending messages to you;
  * To provide you with the type of services you order;
  * To provide you with marketing news and offers when/if applicable;
  * To gather information for statistical analysis and research;
  * To respond to any complaints and comments addressed to our website.

## Legal Basis for Handling Your Data

Buy essay friend handles your personal information only because it has a legal basis to do so and here are the grounds for this:

  * The handling of clients’ personal information is necessary to fulfill the contract between you and our company;
  * Your consent is necessary to let us make particular types of processing like marketing.

The legitimate interest in:

  * Protecting the safety of your personal account;
  * Protecting our service and customers from any attempts to make fraud transactions;
  * Providing you with constant Customer Support.

## Your Consent

We ask for your consent before meddling in your personal data. After giving your consent, you may withdraw it at any time you wish by contacting our Customer Support (support@buyessayfriend.com). Please note that in case we need your personal information so as to provide you with our services and manage our website, but you hesitate to provide us with these details, our services will become unavailable to you.

## What Kind of Personal Information We Gather

We ask you to provide us with information by filling out the order form or communicating with us via phone, email, chat, etc. This includes both personal and non- personal information like:

  * Name;
  * Email;
  * Password;
  * Phone number;
  * Information about your academic profile.

This basic information is necessary to let us contact you and make a contract between you and our service so we could carry out all legal obligations mentioned in it.

If you wish, you may also provide us with additional details like:

  * Date of birth;
  * Place of birth;
  * Gender;
  * Academic level;
  * Field of study;
  * Family status.

The main reason for gathering such information from our clients is to allow us improve the services we render, hence providing quality customer support.

## Third Parties that May Have Access to Your Personal Data

  * Our affiliates

We may transfer your information within a group of subsidiary companies to enable us to provide you with quality services.

  * Our service providers

Your personal information might be shared with third party services that complete transactions, process payments, billing, auditing, marketing and customer support. We make sure that these people take appropriate measures to keep your data safe.

  * Other

We may share your personal information with other parties in the following cases: a) if you allow us to do so; b) to fulfill any necessary legal procedure or responsibility; c) to fulfill any point of the ‘Terms of Use’ policies; d) to fulfill our judicial obligations.

Also, we may share your information in case of merging, reconfiguration, selling, handing over or any similar event that may occur. We guarantee that we will never share or handle your information without getting your consent.

## Where the Data Is Processed

The third parties that we may share your personal data with, may be located in countries with a different jurisdiction than the one of the country you reside in. These are the countries that are not part of the EEA (European Economic Area).

In some cases, these jurisdictions have different security measures and sometimes the jurisdiction of your country is safer. This Privacy Policy ensures that we provide you with the highest level of security. Your personal information cannot be transferred, processed or stored beyond the EEA territory without your permission.

## Cookies

We use cookies to make sure that your user experience is on the highest level. To learn more about the way we use cookie files, please read our Cookie Policy.

## Google Adwords and Google Analytics

We use Google Adwords and Google Analytics to carry out the web analysis. Google Analytics uses cookie files and helps us to analyze the way you use our resource. This means that information about your behavior on our website is rendered to the American Google server. In return, Google evaluates your actions and provides us with a report.

Also, Google and Google Analytics may use information located in your personal Google account to show you the type of advertising material you may be interested in. This happens if you allow Google to use the information from your browser history and apps. The information gathered from your Google account is used to create the lists of audience and perform the cross-device marketing. Therefore, you will see the advertisements on any device which is connected to your Google Account.

We use Google Adwords to track the cookie files in order to display your related ads while you are surfing the Internet, which is related to the Google Content Network.

Our clients may stop the use of cookies at any moment by changing the settings in their web browser. However, note that this may influence the proper functionality of our site.

Remarketing strategies that we apply are used only to give you additional information and promotions basing on your previous experience. You are free to ask us to stop using your personal information for the direct marketing aims.

## Opting-out and Marketing

If you receive your agreement, we may send you text messaging about special offers, promotions, and services via email.

If you don’t want to receive such messages in your inbox, you are free to contact our Support team (support@buyessayfriend.com) or press the “Unsubscribe” button at the bottom of an email you get.

## Your Rights

You have rights with regard to your personal information you provide us with. Bear in mind that we may ask you to verify your identity prior to taking the actions below:

  * The right to access your personal information;
  * The right of rectification, correction, and updating;
  * The right to remove your data in case: a) you declare “off” the processing of your information for direct marketing purposes; b) you declare “off” the data processing and there are no legitimate reasons for processing; c) your data has been processed in an illegitimate way;
  * The right to limit the processing of your information, for example, in case you have provided wrong data;
  * The right to stop the processing of your personal information based on our legitimate reasons;
  * The right to refuse to be a subject to an automated processing, like where a computer software is making decisions which interfere with your contractual rights;
  * The right to information portability. You may get your personal information you have previously provided to us in a machine-readable format. Such data can be transferred to another controller in a secure way.

Every request that relates to changes and exercising of customers’ rights will be dealt with in accordance to the circumstances of a particular case. Please be aware that we may use your personal information to settle disputes, respond to legal commitments and ensure that all the agreement points are met. All requests can be sent to our Customer Support.

## Customer complaints

In case of any concerns about our terms of data collection, feel free to file a complaint to a higher authority such as the Commissioner for Personal Data Protection.

1 Iasonos str., 1082 Nicosia

P.O.Box 23378, 1682 Nicosia

Tel: +357 22818456

Fax: +357 22304565

Email: commissioner_dataprotection.gov.cy

## Children

Buy essay friend doesn’t provide any services to children under 14 years old. No person younger than 14 years old is supposed to share personal information with us. Also, we do not gather information from children under 14 years of age for any purpose. If you are below 14 years, you should keep away from this website, making orders or leaving any of your personal data like phone number, name, e-mail address, home address, nickname or any other.

In case we find out that a child under 14 years old has provided personal information to us, this information will immediately be erased. And, if you suspect that there is any information about/from children under 14 years on our website, please contact our Customer Support (support@buyessayfriend.com).

## Final provisions

To process the information submitted along with an order/inquiry form, we use the SSL certificate, which guarantees that your data and transactions are confidential and safe. We take all possible measures and efforts to keep clients’ information safe from any third parties. All members of our company are well informed and trained to keep the confidentiality of customers’ data.

This Privacy Policy guarantees absolute understanding between our clients and us. Neither we, nor you can have confidence in any details expressed orally or in a written form outside this Privacy Policy. We have the right to change, revise and adjust this document at our discretion but with a prior notice.

## Contacts

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or any other aspects of the way our service works, feel free to contact us:

Email: [support@buyessayfriend.com](mailto:support@buyessayfriend.com)

Phone number: +1(872) 225 3015
